<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <Override>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ It's possible to milk Molochs while they are alive using the proper tool. Be careful not to make any loud noise...</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ Raw food is edible, but of low nutritional value and full of parasites. Always prefer cooked meals.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ You can improve your cooking skills by reading magazines and recipe books.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ If your Butchery skill is low, you may fail harvest meat from a corpse. Every failed swing may result in less meat in total.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ Poor hygiene, sleep and mood will lower your skills. A healthy worker is a productive worker.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ Human meat is still meat, but will cause an unhealthy craving...</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ You can splice fruits together at a research station, giving you seeds with unique properties.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ You can stuff your stomach with food to prevent hunger and gain more food buffs, but those extra calories will be consumed twice as fast.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ Mutated fruits can sometimes be blended into special cocktails with powerful effects.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ It's possible to slowly sleep off addictions, cravings and other minor afflictions. Sometimes rest is the best medicine.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ If you want to learn cooking, you can experiment with food by loading the Test Kitchen in the submarine editor.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ Compared to Vanilla, plants will produce more fruit, but need more attention and care, especially if you use fertilizer.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ If you are using Dynamic Europa (you should!), you will find a food store at Hydroponic stations.</loadingscreentip>
    <loadingscreentip>‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ No clowns were hurt in the making of clown juice.</loadingscreentip>
  </Override>
</infotexts>